<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salva Alcántara</title>
    <link>http://salvalcantara.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Salva Alcántara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017 Salva Alcántara</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 17:32:32 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://salvalcantara.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The IOTA Song</title>
      <link>http://salvalcantara.com/blog/the-iota-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 17:32:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://salvalcantara.com/blog/the-iota-song/</guid>
      <description>Among the different cryptocurrencies out there, I feel very excited about what IOTA can bring to the table. Perhaps in the future I can find the time to write about it from a technical perspective and make a real contribution to its community. Today&amp;rsquo;s post is just to have some fun while the sleeping giant takes the world by storm.
The genesis. One day my brother played a song from basshunter on his phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://salvalcantara.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 19:53:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://salvalcantara.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Salva Alcántara. I currently live in Rubí (Barcelona), Spain, with my beautiful wife and son. I studied Computer Science (Engineering) at the Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona. At the same university, I pursued a PhD on Industrial Informatics &amp;amp; Automatic Control.
During my thesis years, I made two research stays: one at the Shanghai Jiao Tong University, supervised by Prof. Weidong Zhang, and the other one at the Norwegian University of Science and Technology, supervised by prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The motherfucker migration</title>
      <link>http://salvalcantara.com/blog/the-motherfucker-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 19:49:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://salvalcantara.com/blog/the-motherfucker-migration/</guid>
      <description>This (my very first) post covers what I&amp;rsquo;ve come to refer as the motherfucker migration in Django. You can find the accompanying code, as well as detailed instructions on how to apply it, here.
For the sake of explanation, let&amp;rsquo;s consider a Django app with the following two (oversimplified) related models:
class Author(models.Model): name = models.CharField(max_length=30, primary_key=True)  class Article(models.Model): title = models.CharField(max_length=140) authors = models.ManyToManyField(Author, related_name=&#39;articles&#39;)  In short, authors write articles, and an article can have one or more authors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>